#### ARMAN DWI PANGESTU

Bandung, Jawa Barat | armandwi.pangestu7@gmail.com | https://armandwipangestu.vercel.app

#### **PROFILE**

I am an Informatics Engineering student at the University STMIK Bandung. I am a **Junior Web Developer**, **Network Technician**, **System Administrator**, and **Cloud Engineer** who is passionate about learning the technologies needed to solve problems, I strive to provide an engaging and functional user experience.

### **EXPERIENCE**

# BANGKIT ACADEMY 2024 BATCH 1 | CLOUD COMPUTING

FEBRUARY 2024 - PRESENT

- Handle deployment on Google Cloud Platform resources for Capstone Project (Infrastructure, Designing Architecture)
- Creating Back-End RESTful API with modern tech stack and secure using Docker, JWT, etc
- Handle DevOps CI/CD Pipeline on deployment using GitHub Actions to build docker image and deploy to Cloud Run

### PT CITRA JELAJAH INFORMATIKA | SYSTEM ADMINISTRATOR

JUNE 2023 – OCTOBER 2023

- Install, configure, and maintain the server
- Handle DNS, Web, Database, and Mail Server
- cPanel
- Virtualization (Proxmox and VMware ESXi)

## PT CITRA JELAJAH INFORMATIKA | NETWORK TECHNICIAN

JUNE 2021 - JUNE 2023

- Analyze, design, and install network needs in buildings, malls, schools, hotels, etc.
- Network Operation Center (NOC)
- Monitoring Traffic

### **EDUCATION**

## UNIVERSITY STMIK BANDUNG | BACHELOR OF INFORMATICS ENGINEERING

SEPTEMBER 2021 - PRESENT

- Software Engineering
- Database
- Internet of Things

# $\mathbf{SMK}\ \mathbf{MERDEKA}\ \mathbf{BANDUNG}\ |\ \mathbf{COMPUTER}\ \mathbf{AND}\ \mathbf{NETWORK}\ \mathbf{ENGINEERING}$

2018 - 2021

- Computer
- Networking

# SKILLS & TOOLS

HTML	Next.js	Linux	VMware
Markdown	PHP	Bash	cPanel
CSS3	Laravel	Apache / Nginx	PowerDNS
Bootstrap	CodeIgniter	Docker	Mikrotik
Tailwind CSS	JWT	Kubernetes	Cisco
JavaScript	MySQL / MariaDB	GCP	Ruijie
TypeScript	PostgreSQL	Terraform	Ubiquiti / Unifi
React.js	Firebase	Grafana	Figma
Node.js	Git	Prometheus	Postman
Express.js	GitHub / GitLab	Proxmox	Arduino